okay so everyone on Bucky's room was telling me that my font was too small so
好了，所以对 布凯屋子里的所有人是 告诉我， 我的字体太小了
this is my new font hopefully it isn't too big it's kind of big when I'm just you know kind of like looking at on the
这是我的新字体， 希望它不是 当我只是时，它太大了 你知道有点像看着
screen but hopefully um I think a lot of you guys had smaller resolution monitors
屏幕，但希望我想的很多 你们有更小的分辨率显示器
so even when you stretch it out to 1080 the video was still kind of small so hopefully um that's a good size if it's
所以即使你 把它 伸展 到1080 视频还是那么小 希望这是一个很好的大小，如果它是
not then just leave a comment and I'll read them and adjust it appropriately but anyways in this video I'm going to
然后不要发表评论，我会 阅读并适当调整 但无论如何，在这个视频中，我要去
show you how to read and write files so what I'm going to do is I'm going to be
向您展示如何 读取和写入文件 我要做的就是我会成为
creating a file first and then I'll show you guys how to read from it so to
首先创建一个文件，然后我会显示 你们 如何 从中读出这么
create a file the first thing we need is a file object again just name it any
我们需要的第一件事是 创建一个文件 一个文件对象 再仅举任何
variable I'm going to name it fw4 file right in other words file create so what
变量我要将它命名为 fw4文件 换句话说，文件创建如此
you do is you set this equal to this function open and what this is going to
你做的是你设置这个等于这个 功能开放，这将是什么
do is it's going to open a file or pretty much prepare a file to be created
做的是它会 打开一个文件或 几乎准备要创建的文件
or written so the first parameter it takes is the name of the file what do
或者写第一个参数吧 take是文件 的名称
you want to name this file that you're creating well I'll just name it sample
你想要命名这个文件 创造良好我只是将它命名为样本
text will create a very simple text file now the next parameter after this it's
文本将创建一个非常简单的文本文件 现在是 它 之后的下一个参数
going to take a couple different characters if you watch my seed
要采取 一些 不同的方式 如果你看我的 种子， 你会看到
tutorials then you guys are already familiar with all these but for this
教程然后你们已经 熟悉所有这些，但为此
tutorial I'm going to show you guys W in are the first one is w which means open a file and write to it so since this
教程我要 告诉 你们W in 第 一个是w，这意味着开放 一个文件并写入它，因此
file isn't created yet it's going to open it and create it and what right
文件尚未 创建，但它会 发生 打开它，创造它 ，什么是 正确的
means is it prepares us to write text to it so of course it's a text file let's
手段是它准备我们编写文本 它当然是一个文本文件让我们
add some text to it now any time you actually work with a file the first
现在添加一些文字给它 任何 时候你 实际上第一个使用文件
thing you do is use your file object mine's named FW and then you write what
你要做的就是使用你的文件对象 我的 名字是 FW，然后 你写了 什么
do you want to do with that file well there are a couple different functions
你想好好处理那个文件吗？ 有几个不同的功能
as you can see but what we're going to do is just write to it basically um it's
你可以看到，但我们要 去做 什么 不只是写它基本上 嗯 这是
like the equivalent of typing on it simple enough and of course what do you
就像在上面打字一样 很简单，当然你是什么
want to write so writing some stuff in text file and also what you can do just like whenever you print out string you
我想这么写一些东西 文本文件，并 同时 你 可以做到 这 喜欢 每当你打印出你的字符串
can use a special character backslash N and that will move to a new line on your
可以使用特殊字符反斜杠 N. 这会转移到 你 的新线上
file pretty sweet so now since we're on a new line we'll go ahead and write
因为我们正在进行，所以现在 很可爱 一条新线我们将继续写下来
something else FW which is our file sample.txt and write something else on
其他东西FW是我们的档案 sample.txt并写上其他内容
this line and we'll just write like I like can you type Bucky bacon and actually we could just put this all on
这一行 我们就像我一样写 就像你可以键入巴基培根 实际上我们可以把这一切都 放在上面
one line but I just wanted to demonstrate that I don't know this is
一行， 但我只是想 证明我不知道这 是
just a cool way to do it all right so whenever we're done working with a
只是一个 很酷的方式 做这 一切的 权利 所以每当我们完成 一个工作
file what we need to do is we need to close our file object so FW close now
文件我们需要做的是我们需要 做的 关闭我们的文件对象，让FW 现在关闭
this doesn't take any parameters what it does is it basically just frees up on the extra memory so you aren't wasting
这不会取任何参数 它基本上只是放松了 额外的记忆， 所以你不浪费
it so this object just isn't sitting around in your computer so now as you
所以这个对象就是不坐着 在你的电脑周围， 所以现在和你一样
can see oh yeah by the way I deleted that image from the last store oh just because I don't know it was making some
我可以通过我删除的方式看到哦 那张图片 来自 上 一家商店哦 因为我 不知道它是在制作 一些
clutter so right now whenever we create this file by running this program you're
每当 我们创造 时，就会如此混乱 通过运行这个程序你的这个文件
going to see a new file appear right here so keep your eye on this whenever I
要看到一个新文件出现正确 在这里，所以 每当我注意这一点
run this see that how it just popped up now let's double click it to check it
运行这个看看它是如何弹出的 现在让我们双击它来检查它
out so what it did is it wrote this line first and then this line and then a bump
它所做的 就是 写下这一行 首先然后这一行，然后一个凹凸
down to a new line pretty sweet so that is how you create files and Python so
下到一个非常甜的新线 是如何创建文件和Python的
now that we know how to write files or create them let me show you how to read
现在我们知道如何写文件或 创建它们让我 告诉你如何阅读
them so in order to read a file you of course need another file object and I'm
他们是为了阅读你的文件 当然需要另一个文件对象，我
just going to name this one fr4 file read you can actually name anything you
只是要 命名 这 一个 FR4文件 读你可以给你任何名字
want but FR is just easy for me to remember now again this is just object
想要，但FR对我来说很容易 现在再次记住这 只是对象
that pretty much represents a file so we need to open some file and this is going
这几乎代表了一个文件，所以我们 需要打开一些文件 就 可以了
to look familiar we'll open sample dot txt so this pretty
看起来很熟悉 我们将打开示例点 txt，这很漂亮
much says okay we're working with this file
很好说 我们正在处理这个文件
then we need to tell Python what we want to do with it well we want to read it
那么我们就需要来 告诉Python我们想要什么 很好地处理它 我们想要阅读它
we're not creating anything we just want to read data from it so the character
我们没有创造任何 我们想要的 东西 以从中读取数据，所以字符
for that is our so now whenever we read all of this data we need somewhere to
因为这 是 我们的所以 现在每当我们读到 我们需要的所有这些数据
store it because we can't just work with it directly in Python so we need a
存储它因为我们不能只使用它 它直接 在Python中，所以我们需要一个
variable to store that entire string so I'm going to store in a variable called
变量来存储 整个字符串 我要存储一个名为的变量
text and just think of this like a normal string variable so what you do is make a variable and set it equal to Fr
文字，只是把它想象成 一个 正常的字符串变量，所以你做的是 创建一个变量并将其 设置为等于Fr.
dot read and what this is going to do is essentially go to your file read all of
点读，这将是做什么的 基本上去你的文件阅读全部
the crap in it and store it in this variable called text so now we can just
它中的垃圾并将其存储在此中 变量称为文本所以现在我们 只要
do anything the text that we would with string variables such as print text or
做任何文字 ，我们将 与 字符串变量，如 打印文本或
anything else so whenever we do this it's going to
还要别的吗 因此，只要我们做到这一点的要
print out the contents of this file on the screen and of course when we're done
打印出该 文件 的 内容 屏幕，当然，当我们完成
remember to close it close and that just closes the file object so now if we read
记得 要 关闭它关闭和刚刚 如果我们阅读，现在关闭文件对象
this check it out in this first little chunk of code we actually created it and
这个在第一个小点检查出来 我们实际创建它的代码块
then this next one we read the information that was in it the text all
接下来我们读了下一篇 所有信息 都在其中
this stuff and then we just took it stored it in a variable and printed it
这个东西然后我们就接受了 将其存储在变量中并打印出来
out on the screen and of course just to be nice to our computer we closed it
在屏幕上，当然只是为了 对我们的电脑很好， 我们关闭它
gave its back memory so simple enough that is how you read and write files and
它的后 记忆非常简单 这就是你如何读写文件和
in the next video what I'm going to show you guys how to do is actually read a
在下一个视频中我要展示的内容 你们该怎么做实际上是读了一个
text file from somewhere on the Internet and this is actually cool whenever
来自Internet上某处的文本文件 这无论何时都很酷
you're like making a bot or web crawler and you want to crawl a bunch of
你喜欢做一个 机器人或网络爬虫 而且你想爬一堆
webpages get the links in storm in a text file I'll show you guys have to do
网页 获取风暴中的链接 文本文件我会告诉你们 要做的事情
that it's like a really simple version of we're going to be making like a
它就像一个 非常简单的版本 我们正在将 要 作出像
really simple version of Google eventually and I mean really simple not
非常简单的谷歌版本 最终，我的意思是非常简单
anywhere that complex but anyways I'll stop rambling now I'll see you guys
任何复杂但无论如何我会 现在停止漫步， 我会看到你们
later
后来